Curriculum Vitae

Wesley White MAAT

59 Scarlett Avenue, Wendover, Bucks, HP22 5BD

M:- 07749 437466 E:- wes.white@hexthelight.co.uk

About Myself

After nearly 10 years in the accounting profession I found a passion for technology and seeing how it can transform lives through automation, which has led to me to want to shift focus from the numbers and to be able to support those who can build those transformative software by implementing the infrastructure and services to be able to make that happen. I am at my best when able to talk strategy and understanding client's requirements but still maintain an excellent level of detail to create the best solution for the client.

Professional Certifications

e-Careers	Comptia Cloud+	March 2021
e-Careers	AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner	May 2021
e-Careers	AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate	October 2021
BPP	AAT Level 4	2019
UX Design Institute	Certified UX Designer	2020

Education

Chesham Grammar School	3 A Levels incl. Maths at grade B	2012
Amersham School	7 GCSE's A*-C	2010

Technical Skills

- Daily use Linux as main operating system including moderate use of the command line to update system packages and run basic commands such as SSH into other machines
- Competent in HTML and CSS with basic JavaScript experience including running an API on a custom webpage hosted on AWS CloudFront
- Competent with the Microsoft Office Suite with intermediate excel experience
- Basic understanding of SQL commands including table joins
- Competent with Windows and can perform basic maintenace with command prompt, familiar and experience with Remote Desktop Connection

Personal Skills

- Able to work both individually or as part of a team to deliver the client requirements effectively
- Committed to providing the best solutions for the client
- Able to break down high level client requirements into the individual pain points and therefore able to suggest and implement the right solution
- Friendly and highly adaptable to the situation in hand
- I am a quick learner and always willing to try different approaches

Achievements

- Successfully migrated the accounting function for an international call centre company to the cloud accounting package Xero across 7 countries and ran training for their UK and Phillipines operations
- Black Belt in Northern Shaolin Chin Wu Kung Fu
- 3rd Place in BCCMA National Championship for Kung Fu
- BCCMA National Championship Good Sportsman Award
- Participated in the Queen's Golden Jubilee Procession

Career History

Cloud Accounting Specialist Hillier Hopkins LLP Feb 2017 – Present

- Oversaw the Sublime bookkeeping entity, building out the systems and processes to be able to support a growing service list and client requirements
- Oversaw all app advisory services within the firm, including moving clients from legacy desktop applications to cloud accounting software such as Xero
- Advised and trained both clients and staff members on new ways of working using automation at the core of the finance function to eliminate manual entry and therefore allow greater accuracy and insights
- Developed and implemented the firm's response to the CBILS loan scheme as a result of the COVID-19 pandemic to allow quick access to cash flow finance for our clients

Trainee Accountant SJD Accountancy Aug 2014 – Feb 2017

- Developed and maintained a client base of 100+ clients as their primary contact for all of their accounting matters
- Designed and implemented an automatic IR35 calculation spreadsheet for those caught by IR35 regulation for easier processing

Junior Accountant Thomas Cox & Co Jan 2013 – Jul 2014

 Reviewed and provided comment on a number of cloud accountancy platforms to identify those that had potential within the market that we should look to implement for our clients

Interests and Hobbies

- In my spare time I am an avid follower of motorsport, including Formula 1, Formula E and Indycar amongst others
- I enjoy cooking in the evenings and finding new recipes to try out
- I am always looking out for new FOSS software to experiment with and improve my usage of Linux
- I am always keen to try and build something new and make my own, from guitars to mechanical keyboards to websites

References available on request